准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
说"啊"
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜指导
统筹
联合监制
监制
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
好了  你们这群死脑筋
All right, you braindead barnacles
把蟹黄堡放下
drop those patties
你们手上的三明治必须跟我走
Your sandwiches are coming with me
啊  好可爱
Aww, so cute
我好想捏捏他的脸
I just want to pinch his face
看看这位宝贝小甜心
Look at this precious, little sweetie
好可爱的脸颊
Those adorable cheeks
好闪亮的大眼睛
That sparkly eye
不要
No
好可爱的屁屁
That adorable tuchus
啊
Aww
住手
Stop
走开
Get away
啊
Aww
我恨这座城
I hate this town
凯伦
Karen
我来猜猜看  又失败了
Let me guess, another failure?
当然又失败了
Of course, another failure
我又要怎么偷到蟹黄堡的秘密配方
How am I supposed to steal the Krabby Patty formula
大家都把我当小可爱
when everybody thinks I'm adorable?
可爱完全让人怕不起来
Cute is no way to inspire fear
除非
Unless
好
Yes
想到了
That's it
我倒要让全裤头村的白痴知道
I'll teach the fools of this town
可爱一样也能怕起来
that cute can be horrific
好了  我的邪恶大作完成了
There, my evil masterwork is complete
一颗蛋
An egg?
我已经吃过早餐了  谢尔顿
I already had breakfast, Sheldon
蛋不重要
It's not the egg
里面的东西才重要
It's what's inside
一个阴险恶毒  心狠手辣的机器人
A robot so diabolical, so devious
而且还可爱到让人一看就会说
so adorable when people see it, they'll have to say
啊
"Aww"
但是那声音
But that sound
会让它变形成一个可怕的怪物
will transform it into a terrifying monster
把那些人都吃掉
that will eat them
看好了
Behold
复仇机器人模型  小可派
Revenge-bot model QT-Pi
好啊
Yes
你刚说它会吃人吗
Did you say it was going to eat people?
没错
That's right
被吃掉的人会被关进它的量子胃监狱里
Its victims will be trapped
in its quantum stomach prison
来
to
反思自己的所作所为
think about what they've done?
那就好好玩你的小玩具去
Well, have fun with your little toy
别忘了拿垃圾出去倒
Just don't forget to take out the trash
啊
Aww
天啊
Oh, boy
成功了
It works
成
It
海之霸专属财产
真见鬼
Barnacles
海之霸
我准备好了
I'm ready
太好了
Excellent
那白痴一定会对我机器人啊个不停
That moron won't be able to stop aww-ing at my robot
上啊  机器人
Go, robot
吃掉他
Eat him
狠狠吃掉他  宝贝
Eat him good, baby
啊
A --
要来了
Here it comes
爱护好你这个可爱小机器人
Cute, little robot like you
可不能让你孤零零地自个在外头待着
shouldn't be out here all alone
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
小可派
QT-Pi?
太可爱了
That's adorable
来吧
Come on
我们一起找主人  顺便让我关照你
I'll take care of you until we find your owner
好  这就对了
Yes, that's right
带我们打入敌人的巢穴
Take us right into my enemy's lair
我就在这上班
This is where I work
这些是我们的客人
These are our customers
这位是章鱼哥  我最好的朋友
And this is Squidward, my best friend
好肮脏的谎言
That is a filthy lie
说到肮脏
Speaking of filthy
得先洗把脏手再去做蟹黄堡
I better wash these dirty hands before I get cooking
章鱼哥  行行好帮我看好他吧
Squidward, be a dear and keep an eye on him for me
好不好
will you?
你可真是太可爱了
Say, you are pretty cute
你说可爱吗
Did you say cute?
好啊
Oh, yeah
他好可爱
He's so cute
都得了
Okay
往后稍稍  畜生们
get back, you animals
把他当宝贝也得给人家空间
He needs room to be precious
啊
Aww
外面不像是大声哭诉自己被宰的喊声
Those don't sound like "I'm spending money" screams
什么
Wha--?
不
No
好好把手擦干
Proper drying of the hands
重要程度堪比
is every bit as important as the--
什么
wha--
看来今天关门挺早的
Guess we closed early today
天啊
Oh, boy
这样就有不少时间
Now I have more time
可以帮我新朋友小可派了
to help my new friend QT-Pi
这到底是怎么回事
What in the name of Neptune is going on here?
对啊  怎么回事呢
Oh, yeah, what is happening here?
痞老板  想必都是你干的好事吧
Plankton, this has you written all over it
别血口喷人
How dare you?
海之霸专属财产
那玩意是怎么挂上去的
How'd that get on there?
好  都是我干的
Okay, it was me
我为了教训你们
To teach you all a lesson
就做了个机器人
I made a robot
专门吃说了啊的人
that eats people who say, "aww"
快告我吧
So sue me
我不想告你  痞老板
I don't want to sue you, Plankton
我要从你的地狱机关里逃出去
I want to get out of your infernal contraption
逃出去的唯一出路
Well, the only way out
就是紧急疏散小舌
is the emergency evacuation uvula
而它就在上面
which is up there
紧急出口
好了  听见小个子说的话了吧
All right, you heard the pipsqueak
大家叠罗汉
Everyone form up
拉动小舌
Let's yank that "uvuler"
看来想要逃出去的话
Looks like we're stuck here
得先等这破机器人多吃点人进来了
until this dumb robot eats more people
兽医
兽医可以帮忙找到你主人
The veterinarian can help me find your owner
既然你是机器人
You're a robot
肯定就有身份芯片了
so you must be chipped
我一般只治动物  不治机器
Normally I work with animals, not machines
不过又有啥区别
but how different can they be?
来听诊一下
Let's just take a listen
说  啊
Say, "Aww"
让它吃你
Get eaten
说  啊
Say, "Aww"
天啊
Oh, my
好吧  说啊
Okay then, say "aww"
啊
Aww
不对  等下
No, wait
我想说的是
I meant to say
好可爱
So cute
手套乐园
什么
What?
买票才能进去
You need to buy a ticket
啊
Aww
热狗
完美  就往这边逃
Perfect, I'll escape through there
死胡同
游乐设施
死胡同游乐设施
A dead end ride?
感觉跟手套主题不怎么搭
That doesn't seem very glove themed
小可派  求你别吃我
QT-Pi, please don't eat me
吃了他
Eat him
我
I--
有了
I know
来使出音乐抚慰人心的神奇力量
I'll try the soothing power of music
啊  该死
Aw, rats
你成功了  小子
You did it, boy
给我准备的惊喜派对
A surprise party for me?
这不是派对  你个笨蛋
This isn't a party, you boob
那我一进来大家怎么都在欢呼
Well, why did everyone cheer when I showed up?
因为有你在的话
Because with you
我们就能够得到紧急逃生小舌了
we can finally reach the emergency escape "uvuler"
好了  大家再来叠罗汉
All right, let's try it again, people
怎么回事
What's going on?
抓到了
Got it
好耶
Yeah
成功了
We did it
逃出来了
We escaped
我让大家免费进手套乐园玩了
And I got us into Glove World for free
不用客气
You're welcome
最后一个上碰碰手套的变臭鸡蛋
Last one on the bumper gloves is a rotten egg
好耶
Yeah
可怜的小可派
Poor QT-Pi
吃掉大家没法帮你解决问题
That whole eating everyone thing
didn't work out for you
我想我知道
I think I know
可以怎样利用你的能力做好事了
how you could use your powers for good
手套发射场
快来试玩
Step right up and try
我们独具手套特色的全新游乐项目
our latest glove-tastic ride
来手套发射场体验世界啊灾难
Experience the aww-pocalypse at the Glove Launch
啊
Aww
好耶
All right
耶耶耶
Yeah, yeah, yeah
你说我太矮不能玩是什么意思
What do you mean I'm too short to ride this ride?
世界啊末日求生成功
准备好再来一轮吗
手套套提醒
长这么高才能玩哦
这可是我发明的
I built this
抱歉  小朋友
Sorry, buddy
规矩就是规矩
Rules is rules
你这种可爱小不点也必须得遵守
even for an adorable little guy like you
可真是可爱
Real cute
邮递员派大星
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
动画总监
指导总监
统筹
联合监制
监制
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
邮件
特别快递
Special delivery
我新石头终于到了
My new rock is finally here
等等
Hold on
圆点
polka dots?
我订的可是纯色
I ordered plaid
你得退回去  邮递员先生
You'll have to take it back, Mr. Mailman
退回去
Back?
邮递员先生
Mr. Mailman?
我的背
My back
没事吧  兄弟
You okay, buddy?
得把邮件送出去
Gotta deliver mail
你现在什么东西都不适合去送
You are in no shape to deliver anything, fella
放松就好  来我家睡吧
Just relax and crash at my place
我今天来帮你送邮件
I'll deliver your mail for you today
差点忘带邮包了
Almost forgot my mail bag
差点忘戴邮递员帽了
Almost forgot my mailman hat
好了
All righty
来看我第一单往哪家送
Let's see where my first delivery is
我看不懂
I can't read this
派大星  一听就知道是你头在撞门
Hey, Patrick, I thought that sounded like your head
海绵宝宝  你知道这个
SpongeBob, do you know where this
嗨绵
Spon-gee-Boob
包包住哪吗
Squir-pa-Nants lives?
从来没听说过
Never heard of him
好吧  退给寄件人
Oh, well, return to sender
你怎么穿了新衣服
What's with the new threads?
我现在是邮递员了
I'm a mailman now
我一直都很想当邮递员
I've always wanted to be a mailman
就好像每天都当圣诞老人一样
It's like getting to be Santa every day
星期天例外
except Sundays
抱歉  海绵宝宝
Sorry, SpongeBob
现在我才是邮递员
but I'm the mailman now
好吧
Okay
不过你可以当我邮递伙伴
But you can be my postal pal
一起来送邮件吧
Let's get mailing
邮递伙伴  你来按门铃
Postal pal, you may ring the doorbell
是的长官
Yes, sir
邮递员长官
Mr. Mailman, sir
先给按门铃的手指热身一下
I better warm up the old bell ringer
上下上下
Up, down, up, down
右边扭扭  左边扭扭
Twist right, twist left
再抹个指甲油
And polish the nail
邮件
Mail
邮局让你们俩白痴送邮件了
They let a moron like you deliver the mail?
邮局让白痴做的事肯定会让你吃惊
You'd be surprised what they let morons do
到货了
It's here
章鱼哥的脸怎么了
What's wrong with Squidward's face?
他好像在笑
I think he's smiling
终于到手了  我的涡轮竖笛
I finally got it, my turbo clarinet
每分钱都值得花
Worth every penny
腌椰菜
很好  下一站到了
Oh, good, our next stop
担任陪审团职务的传票
A summons for jury duty
运气真好
Lucky
特别快递
Special delivery
干的漂亮  邮递员先生
Great job, Mr. Mailman
这投信口一定有毛病
Must be a defective mail slot
这样应该就行了
That ought to do it
还是按门铃试试看吧
Maybe I'll just try the doorbell
需要帮忙吗
Can I help you?
特别快递
Special delivery
我不要
I don't want it
还是跳过这家  送下一家的邮件吧
Maybe we should just move on to the next house
不行
No
我是邮递员
I am a mailman
邮递誓词有言
Like the postal oath says
不管是上刀山下火海
neither bunions or onions nor ditches or dangers
我都要把邮件送出去
will stop me from giving stuff to strangers
特别快递
Special delivery
可别给我递
Special un-delivery
当邮递员跟当圣诞老人就不是一回事
Being a mailman isn't like being Santa Claus at all
我们是胡须兄弟
We're beard bros
鱼诞快乐
Merry Fishmas
现在七月
It's July
收封信吧
Just take a letter
我不要
I don't want it
上刀山下火海
Neither bunions or onions
给我收信
Take your mail
我要狠狠编你码
I'll zip your code so hard
接招
En garde
接糕
En lard
我要贴你邮票
I'm gonna stamp you
寄给你一套屁递
I'll send you butt express
你公民义务是逃不掉的
You can't run from your civic duties
收下
Get it
打我可以  退回不行
slap back, no take backs
不错
Not bad
这传票是海霸王的
This summons is for Bubble Bass
你们这俩白痴
you nincompoops
来了
Coming
别走
Don't leave
快到了
Almost there
天啊  从来没人来我家
Oh, boy, I never get visitors
寄给特别老人家的特别快递
Special delivery for one special, old man
我找不到寄给他的信
I can't find any mail for him
我从来没收到信
I never get any mail
太悲伤了
That's so sad
给他送点别人的邮件  好吗
Let's give him some of the other mail, huh?
找到寄给你的信了  助步器老头
I found a letter for you, Old Man Walker
助步器老头
我被征召了
I've been drafted
天啊
Oh, boy
取消赎回权
就这么一封信能让他这么高兴
If one letter made him this happy
把所有邮件都给他一定会高兴到爆
I bet all of the mail will make him explode with joy
好啊
Sure
全都是寄给我的吗
all of this for me?
接下来要送到哪  邮递员派大星
What's next, Postman Patrick?
邮件都送光了
We're all out of mail
去问问那辆冰淇淋车
Let's ask that ice cream truck
看它知不知道要去哪找邮件
if it knows where to find some mail
那不是冰淇淋车
That's no ice cream truck
是邮车
It's a mail truck
真的吗
Really?
我还以为大卡车都是女孩子
I thought all trucks were girls
开邮车中大奖
We hit the postal jackpot
酷
Cool
那俩怪人偷了我邮车
Those weirdos stole my truck
快追那俩偷信贼
Follow those postal pilferers
特别快递
A special delivery
给弗雷德的特别快递
Special delivery for Fred
谁是卡罗尔
Who's Carol?
卡罗尔
这个给你  佩妮
This one's for you, Penny
太好了
Great
我买的充气船终于到了
The raft I ordered has finally arrived
海盗
Pirates
什么
Wha--?
为什么海盗穿得好像邮递员
Why are these pirates dressed like mail people?
他们想偷邮件
They want to steal our mail
驱逐入侵者
Repel the boarders
正在驱逐入侵者  长官
Repelling boarders, sir
哈罗德
Harold
不
No
送点货到付款
I'm shipping these COD
货倒复垮
Crash on delivery
空运要来了
And here comes some air mail
又是海霸王的陪审团传票
Another jury summons for Bubble Bass
特别快递
Special delivery
只剩垃圾邮件了
All we have left is junk mail
放心
Don't worry
进了邮局  他们绝对找不到我们
They'll never find us in this post office
邮局
裤头村监狱
今天的邮件来了  狱长
Here's today's mail, warden
特别快递
Special delivery